Guide to the United Mission to Nepal Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- G, Series VII
  - Gorkha Project
    - General: Reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.02/0050- G-02.01.02/0062, 1987 Sep- 1989 Jan (Box 63, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes for hospital and CHP; Proposed planning and project structure; Detailed plans; Rural development trip report; Detailed annual reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.02/0063- G-02.01.02/0076, 1989 Jan 31- 1990 Feb (Box 63, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes; Reports on visits to CDO, etc.; Fuel shortages; Storm damages; Detailed annual reports; Visit to Gorkha; Nutrition Consultant's visit
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.03/0001- G-02.01.03/0009, 1990 Jun- 1991 Feb (Box 63, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Paper on CHP development; OPD Clinical information system; Hospital mission statement; Detailed annual reports; Project PMC minutes; Family planning in AP
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.03/0010- G-02.01.03/0019, 1991 Feb 19-Aug (Box 63, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes; Detailed plans for 1991/92; Telephone connection correspondence; Primary health care study; Proposed project structure; Vaccination records 1987-1990; CHP senior staff skills development program; Proposal for project management review
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.03/0020- G-02.01.03/0025, 1991 Sep- 1992 Mar (Box 63, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Nutrition visit report; NFE plans and budget; Proposal for project management review; Hospital mid year report; Detailed annual plans; PMC meeting
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.03/0026- G-02.01.03/0031, 1992 Aug- 1993 Jan (Box 63, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Detailed annual report; Report on vaccination coverage; PMC meetings; Report on ultrasound; NFE visit report; Hospital mid-year reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.03/0032- G-02.01.03/0035, 1993 Feb- 1993 Aug (Box 63, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Plans for 1993/94; PMC meeting; Detailed annual report; PMC meeting
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.04/0001 - G-02.01.04/0010, 1993 Feb- 1994 Apr (Box 64, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Nutrition visit report; Medical student elective program; Monthly hospital statistics for 1993; PMC meeting; Summary and detailed annual plans 1994/95 and mission statement
      - Reports, etc. - Re. 25th anniversary of hospital: G-02.01.04/0010, 1994 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.04/0011 - G-02.01.04/0020, 1994 Apr- 1995 Jan (Box 64, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: CHP quarterly report; Contract of mutual agreement with District Health Office; Summary and detailed annual reports; Summary hospital statistics; PMC meeting; CHP quarterly and mid-year reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.04/0021 - G-02.01.04/0029, 1995 Feb- Nov (Box 64, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Summary and detailed plans; PMC meeting; Proposal: Enhancing Primary Health Care; Hospital and CHP reviews; CHP quarterly report; CHP household results
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.04/0030 - G-02.01.04/0043, 1995 Nov- 1996 Jul (Box 64, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Hospital mid-year report; Hospital annual plan; Extended POM minutes; PMC meeting; Darkness to light: NFE in Nepal; HRD workshop
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.04/0044 - G-02.01.04/0053, 1996 Jul- 1997 Feb (Box 64, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Reports; EPC meeting (PMC) and staff association report; Hospital LTP and Vision 1997-2004; Options for future Gorkha project
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.05/0001 - G-02.01.05/0011, 1997 Feb- 1997 Jul (Box 64, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Hospital annual plan 1997/98; Hospital project plan 1997/98; Hospital PMC meeting; School roof blown off in storm
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.05/0012 - G-02.01.05/0026, Jul 1997- 1998 Mar (Box 64, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Report on DOTS; Hospital and CHP overviews; CHP mid-year report; Plans; Minutes
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.05/0027 - G-02.01.05/0034, 1998 Apr- Sep (Box 64, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Household survey; Project description; Guidelines for an emergency; CHP detailed summary and annual report
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.05/0035 - G-02.01.05/0044, 1998 Oct-1999 Feb (Box 64, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Response to the present political climate; CHP quarterly report to Oct 1998; Hospital PMC minutes; CHP PMC minutes
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.05/0045 - G-02.01.05/0051, 1999 Feb- Jun (Box 64, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: CHP summary 3 year plan 2000-2003 and Summary annual plan 1999-2000; CHP quarterly report to mid-April; Reasons for lower patient numbers; Future of hospital
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.06/0001 - G-02.01.06/0006, 1999 Jul-Aug (Box 65, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Project description; Hospital summary and detailed annual reports 1998/1999; CHP summary and detailed annual reports 1998/1999; Project activity report; CHP quarterly report to mid-July 1999
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.06/0007 - G-02.01.06/0010, 1999 Aug- Dec (Box 65, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Staff resignations; CHP quarterly reports to mid-Oct and mid-December 1999; Mid-year report 1999/2000
      - Reports, etc.: Hospital and Community Health Project (G-02.01), 1991-2001 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - General: Sections
      - Barpak; Devkot: G-02.02.01/0001 - G-02.02.01/0021, 1965 Apr- 1988 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Lamagara; Lamjung:: G-02.02.01/0022 - G-02.02.01/0023, 1981 Mar- 1989 Jul (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Tuberculosis (TB) Control program: G-02.02.01/0024 - G-02.02.01/0041, 1987-1994 (Box 65, Folder 6-7)
      - Leadership/PCC Meetings: G-02.02.01/0042, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Education: Reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.03.01/0001 - G-02.03.01/0030, 1974 Dec- 1999 Dec (Box 66, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: General; New Era; AMP Pipal; Bandipur; Gankhu; Lapsibot; Luitel; Makaisingh
      - Reports,etc.- New Era Final Report: G-02.03.01/0008, 1982 (Box 162, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc. - Village profile of Thalajung: G-02.03.01/0038 (Box 162, Folder 5)
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.03.01/0031 - G-02.03.01/0047, 1980 Aug- 1991 Apr (Box 66, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Thalajung (see also General and Agriculture files under Gorkha: reports, plans, RDC visit report, monthly reports, Adult literacy case study
    - Education: Correspondence
      - Correspondence: G-02.04.01/0001 - G-02.04.01/0034 - RESTRICTED, 1974-1990 (Box 66, Folder 8-10)
      - Correspondence: G-02.04.02/0001 - G-02.04.02/0028 - RESTRICTED, 1968-1989 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
    - Agriculture: Reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.05.01/0001 - G-02.05.01/0019, 1961 Jan- 1970 May (Box 66, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Report and plan: "Community development in Gorkha- Agriculture"; Buying a buffalo; Notes on agriculture work in Gorkha; Report on visit by Portzes; Reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.05.01/0020 - G-02.05.01/0036, 1971 Jul- 1985 Dec (Box 66, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Closing down of Agriculture program; Tea plantation in Thalajung; Reports; Orientation trip to AP; Options for agriculture and forestry; Future of farm and water projects
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.05.01/0037 - G-02.05.01/0044, 1986 Feb- 1989 Dec (Box 66, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Future agriculture activities of CHP and report on PMC; RDC trip report; Study and assessment of agriculture work in AP 1959-1971; Pulling it all together
    - Agriculture: Correspondence
      - Correspondence, etc.: G-02.06.01/0001 - G-02.06.01/0017 - RESTRICTED, 1963-1983 (Box 67, Folder 5-7)
    - General: Correspondence
      - Correspondence, etc.: G-02.07.01/0001 - G-02.07.01/0021 - RESTRICTED, 1957 -1966 (Box 67, Folder 8-10)
      - Correspondence, etc.: G-02.07.01 - RESTRICTED (Box 68, Folder 1-4)
      - Correspondence, etc.: G-02.07.02 - RESTRICTED, 1966-1975 (Box 68, Folder 5-9)
      - Correspondence, etc.: G-02.07.03/0001 - G-02.07.03/0035 - RESTRICTED, 1971-1985 (Box 69, Folder 1-5)
      - Correspondence, etc.: G-02.07.04/0001 - G-02.07.04/0014 - RESTRICTED, 1984-1988 (Box 65, Folder 8-9)
      - Correspondence, etc.: G-02.07.04/0015- G-02.07.04/0027 - RESTRICTED, 1988-1999 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
    - Community Health Project
      - Non-formal education (G-02.09), 1994-1995 (Box 200, Folder 7)
      - IAC / IMC Minutes (G-02.09), 1992-2001 (Box 200, Folder 8)
      - Lamjung CHP reports (G-02.09), 1999-2004 (Box 201, Folder 1-2)
    - Amp Pipal Hospital
      - Reports, correspondence, incl. re. closure (Maoist threat) - (G-02.10) - RESTRICTED, 1996, 2000-2001, 2003-2005 (Box 201, Folder 3-4)
  - Gifts, Miscellaneous
    - Gifts, other than financial: G-03.00.01, 1964- 1976 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Gossner Mission
    - Correspondence: G-04.00.01, 1968 Feb- 2000 Mar (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Government, Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence, etc. G-05.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1961 May- 2000 Jul (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Request from PM's office: (G-05.00), 2002 (Box 201, Folder 5)
- H, Series VIII
  - Headquarters
    - General administration
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.01.01/0001 - H-01.01.01/0084 - RESTRICTED, 1958 -1992 (Box 70, Folder 1-6)
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.01.02/0001 - H-01.01.02/0042 - RESTRICTED, 1992 -2000 (Box 70, Folder 7-9)
      - Meeting minutes: (H-01.01), 2001-2005 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Central Services Department
      See also HQ Administration, Gorkha Freight file, Gorkha and Okl. general
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.02.01/0001 - H-01.02.01/0056 - RESTRICTED, 1966- 1999 (Box 71, Folder 1-3)
    - Land and Buildings
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.03.01/0001 - H-01.03.01/0028 - RESTRICTED, 1959-1997 (Box 71, Folder 8-11)
      - Lease on five buildings: H-01.03.02/0008 - RESTRICTED, 1971 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, agreements with Himal Hydro: (H-01.03) - RESTRICTED, 2000-2009 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Finance Department
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.04.01/0001 - H-01.04.01/0075 - RESTRICTED, 1964-1998 (Box 71, Folder 4-6)
    - Circulars re. Plans and Budgets / Reports
      - Budgets - RESTRICTED, 2000-2004 (Box 185, Folder 2)
      - Plans, reports, etc.: (H-01.05), 1999-2005 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Guesthouses/ Serviced Accommodation
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.06.01/0051 - H-01.06.01/0051 - RESTRICTED, 1969-1998 (Box 73, Folder 1-3)
        Usha Niketan, Asha Niketan, Bishwas Niketan, Salyan House, Prem Sadan, Flemmig House, Puchlo Newas
      - Reports, etc.: (H-01.06), 2001-2006 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Staff meetings
      - Minutes: H-01.07.01 (Box 72, Folder 2-9)
      - Minutes: H-01.07.02, 1982-1998 (Box 73, Folder 4-6)
    - Development and Missionwide Support Project (MSP)
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.08.01/0001 - H-01.08.01/0020 - RESTRICTED, 1984-1997 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Publications/ Communication Office
      See also below under U: UMN Publications
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.09.01/0001 - H-01.09.01/0015, 1987-1999 (Box 71, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Developing a Public Relations office for UMN; Plan to establish a Communication Office with UMN; The establishment of the Communications office with UMN; Revised annual plan
    - Personnel Department
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-01.10.01/0001 - H-01.10.01/0017, 1992-1999 (Box 72, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Strategic planning for the Personnel Department (PD); Changes in PD, and introduction to PD; Report; Overview; Annual reports; PC minutes; Strategic Plans; Annual Plans
      - Employee Relations leaflets, 2000,n.d. (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Operations Department
      Includes AGNW, Archives, Communications, Disaster Preparedness & Tri-Agency, Missionwide Support Project
      - Plans, reports: (H-01.11), 2002-2003 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Learning Centre/ Learning Resource Centre
      - Plans, reports: (H-01.12), 2004-2005 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Technical Services
      - Plans, reports: (H-01.13, 2000-2005 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Health Services
    - General: Reports, etc
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.01/0001 - H-02.01.01/0027, 1955- 1969 Nov (Box 73, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Plans for extension of medical work; Summarized description of all projects; List of beds and staff; Outline of medical services of UMN; Review of health services work
      - Reports., etc.: H-02.01.01/0017, 1965 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.01/0028 - H-02.01.01/0046, 1970- 1972 Jun (Box 73, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Report of Workers' Conference medical group; Review of Nepal medical services; HMG statistics and plans; UMN personnel statistics for HMG; Suggestion of hospital in West Nepal; Summary of discussion on abortion
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.01/0047 - H-02.01.01/0069, 1972 Jul- 1976 Jan (Box 73, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Problems in practical patient management in Nepal; Severe acute mountain sickness; Number of nurses in Nepal; Papers on family planning; Details of UMN projects and staff; Standards of staffing in HMG work; Role of mission health services; Experiences of a medical elective in Nepal
      - Reports, etc. - Proposal for Central Research Office of UMN: H-02.01.01/0068, 1976 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.01/0070 - H-02.01.01/0086, 1976 May- 1977 (Box 73, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Suggested policy guidelines; HSB planning session; Evaluation report on the activities of BNMT; Professional orientation; Notes on nurses offering for work in Nepal with UMN
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.01/0087 - H-02.01.01/0102, 1977- 1978 (Box 73, Folder 11)
        Including regarding: Professional orientation week; Board dinner planned for HSB; First national TB seminar; HMG health administration, etc.
      - Reports, etc. - Literacy health teaching, 3 booklets: H-02.01.01/0101, 1978 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.01 (Box 159, Folder 5)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.02/0001 - H-02.01.02/0018, 1979 Feb- 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: HSB agenda notes; Health and medical information sheet, Nepal; Round and about; Report on HSB and finances; Thoughts on turning over to HMG; Facing TB problems in Nepal; Continuing education; Visual aids consultation meeting
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.02/0019 - H-02.01.02/0039, 1980 Aug- 1981 (Box 74, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Report on nurse staffing situation, etc.; Long term health plan; Maternity teaching; Surgery in a mission hospital; Round and about; Papers on antibiotics; Appropriate health care; Basic data definitions
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.02/0040 - H-02.01.02/0069, 1981 Oct- 1983 Dec (Box 74, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Report on HSB; Nepali staff figures for 1980 and 1981; Staff medical insurance; X-ray in UMN hospitals; Family planning meeting and notes; Funding appeal letter; Financial management in hospitals
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.02/0070 - H-02.01.02/0094, 1983 Dec- 1984 Oct (Box 74, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Rotation of nurses on bond; Discussion on care levels; Mountain sickness paper; Report on HSB; Continuing education; Information in letters regarding funding UMN's contribution to hospital care in Nepal; Statistical reports
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.02/0095 - H-02.01.02/0120, 1984 Oct- 1985 Nov (Box 74, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Brief report from projects; Workshop on NGO's, Molt invitation; Minutes of informal meeting on physiotherapy discussion; Health Care Consultant proposal; HSB discussion groups; Orientation to HSB; Vellore Committee
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.03/0001 - H-02.01.03/0022, 1985 Nov- 1986 Dec (Box 74, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Pathology and lab. survey; Reports on HSB and EC; Worker's Conference discussion papers; Orientation to HSB; Care levels in hospitals; Policies and reporting systems; Plans and reports definitions
      - Reports, etc. - "Over Thirty": H-02.01.03/0017, 1986 (Box 160, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.03/0023 - H-02.01.03/0046, 1986 Dec- 1988 May (Box 74, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Poverty and poor health: an intimate relationship; How to make a toilet (Nepali leaflet); Agencies involved in health; TB leaflet; Factors affecting health in Nepal; Copy of HS agreement with HMG
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.03/0047 - H-02.01.03/0065, 1988 Jun- 1989 Aug (Box 74, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Case study reports; Division of responsibilities in HSO; General orientation to Nepal and health; Departure of T. Strong, HSS; Correspondence on Scope of HS agreement
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.03/0066 - H-02.01.03/0078, 1989 Sep- 1990 Aug (Box 74, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: UMN's role in running hospitals; Teaching physiotherapy to nurses; Operating trends in hospitals; Trend predictions; Correspondence with Royal Government in Bhutan on training of pharmacy students
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.04/0001 - H-02.01.04/0017, 1990 Jul- 1991 Jun 3 (Box 75, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Hospitals' most common diagnosis/ HS presentation to the Board; HEEd policies; Geographical spread, attending patients, UMN hospitals; HSD current trends; Health/ Training Coordinator's workshop; Jeevan Jal
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.04/0018 - H-02.01.04/0034, 1991 Jun 8- Dec (Box 75, Folder 2)
        Including regarding; Copy of new health agreement; Sanitation workshop, SSNCC; SW PMC minutes; Drug resistant typhoid; Health economics and health sector in Nepal; List of workshop and conferences for UMN HS staff
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.04/0035 - H-02.01.04/0052, 1991 Dec- 1993 Aug (Box 75, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: SW PMC minutes; Substance abuse; Nepal Cancer Relief Society; Vision for UMN's hospital involvement; General paper on HS of UMN; Medical elective program restarted in February
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.04/0053 - H-02.01.04/0061, 1993 Sep- 1994 Mar (Box 75, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: HSD organisation; Health issues in Nepal: Dangers of being a mother; New technologies in medicine; Medical case studies
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.04/0062 - H-02.01.04/0078, 1994 Mar- Dec (Box 75, Folder 5)
        Including regarding: Report on CBR forum; Maternal mortality; H.S. Consultation; MAF paper; HSO summary annual report (general); HS general description; Papers on the Plague; Towards the future
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.05/0001 - H-02.01.05/0015, 1995 Jan- 1995 Nov (Box 75, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: HSD Review; Suggested curriculum for nurse aids; Short course training in ultra sound: Presentation of certificates; Leprosy NGO network meeting; Towards the future update
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.05/0016 - H-02.01.05/0030, 1995 Dec- 1996 Nov (Box 75, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Report of EHA meeting; Hospitals towards the future: update; Safe Motherhood program of UMN; Family planning update; Papers on Consultation for development of Compensation Differentials
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.05/0031 - H-02.01.05/0046, 1997- 1998 (Box 75, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Impatient discharge database; Correspondence on wheelchairs; Kangaroo nursing; Sectoral networks in Nepal; Formation of Consultancy Team; INPAT hospital monitoring computer program
      - Reports, etc. - Inpatient Discharge Database: H-02.01.05/0033, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.05/0047 - H-02.01.05/0052, Apr- Sep 1998 (Box 75, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: Occupational therapy in Nepal: A Short-termer's experience; NGO Coordinating Council meeting and Rehab, contract and reports; Report and visit to Vellore; HS management and support plan
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.05/0053 - H-02.01.05/0069, 1998 Oct- 1999 Jul (Box 75, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Review of integrated management of childhood illnesses; Training activities in UMN medical institutions in 1998; Community Drug Program; UMN hospitals essential equipment replacement fund
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.01.06/0001 - H-02.01.06/0006, 1999 Aug- Dec (Box 76, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: HSD Review; HSD overview; HS Week; UMN hospitals essential equipment replacement; Technical working group for Hospital Assessment Consultancy meeting
      - Reports, plans, etc.: (H-02.01), 1996-2004 (Box 202, Folder 5-8)
      - Hospital newsletters, various; "Health Services in Nepal" brochure, Medical Assistance Fund brochures, Hospitals' Endowment Trust brochure, 1989-2010 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - General: Correspondence
      - Correspondence, etc.: H-02.02.01/0001 - H-02.02.01/0016 - RESTRICTED, 1969 -1994 (Box 76, Folder 5-7)
    - Community Health General
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.03.01/0001 - H-02.03.01/0023, 1962 Apr- 1975 (Box 76, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Outline plans for mobile unit; Helath program for Nepal; Approved guidelines for Community Health (CH) work; Community Health Committee minutes; Proposal for public health workers; Report of planning sessions; Revised principles for development
      - Reports, etc. - Interviews by Nursing students: H-02.03.01/0014/001, 1972 (Box 158, Folder 3)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.03.01/0024 - H-02.03.01/0040, 1975- 1978 (Box 76, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: HMG health map; The Bible and the health of the community; Principles for achieving primary health care; Community health and TB control program; Some indicators for evaluation of CH impact; Involvement in CH; Sample form for community diagnosis
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.03.01/0027/001, 1976 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc. - Flash cards, etc.: H-02.03.01/0028/001, 1976 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.03.01/0041 - H-02.03.01/0059, 1978- 1985 (Box 77, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: Community nurse midwife auxiliary; Working with Health Posts; Evaluation of LTP targets; Visual aid workshop report; Ongoing evaluation of CHPs; CH workshop report; Guidelines on data collection; Some more rules for social surveys
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.03.01/0060 - H-02.03.01/0062, 1976-1985 (Box 77, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: HMG map, 1984; HASP Compost toilet; Section on EPI
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.03.01/0063 - H-02.03.01/0079, 1986 Mar- 1989 Aug (Box 77, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Vision health care; CHP seminar; The Village health workers; Measurable indicators of CHPs; The purpose and planning of CHPs
      - Reports, etc.: H-02.03.02/0001 - H-02.03.02/0019, 1989 Mar- 1999 Jun (Box 77, Folder 4)
        Including regarding: Scope of activities associated with HS agreement; Comments for Community Development Seminar; Childbirth survey, Chapter 3 (draft); Project on population and family health project; CH workshop report; CH consultation; Share and Care magazine
      - Reports,etc. - "Phukal, Mantras and oil" - H-02.03.02/0015, 1997 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Health Services Board SOWRs
      - Drafts and approved SOWRs: H-02.04.01/0001 - H-02.04.01/0006, 1975 Jul- 1985 Oct (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Health Services Board Meetings:
      - Meeting agendas; Appointment letters; etc: H-02.05.01 - RESTRICTED, 1976 May- 1987 Feb (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Bound volumes of Health Services Board minutes, 1976-1987 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Health Services Board Evaluation
      - Outline, minutes, reports: H-02.06.01/0001 - H-02.06.01/0017, 1984 Mar- 1986 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Health Services Projects: History and Statistics
      - Historical notes made from annual plans and reports with statistical charts: H-02.07.01/0001 - H-02.07.01/0006 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)